Minh Nguyen

Graphic Designer / Marketing Coordinator

Phone: (512) 825 9661

Email: MinhStudios@gmail.com
Portfolio: www.Minhstudios.com
Linkedin.com/in/minhstudios

Summary

A Graphic designer with eight years of professional experience focused on print, illustration, logo, and web design. Minh also has experience with WordPress, Bootstrap, photography, drawing, and painting. He aims to have a continued advancement in web development as part of his goal set. After getting his BFA at Texas State University and completing an internship in San Antonio (Clockwork Studios), Minh began working in-house for a Real Estate firm where he was immersed in website design, real estate photography, print, and direct mail. After some contract work, he soon became a marketing coordinator for Newmark Knight Frank and works with reputable clients to market their commercial real estate assets.

Experience

MARKETING COORDINATOR | DEC 2017 - SEPT 2020 Newmark Knight Frank, Austin, TX (Tasks/*Achievements)

- » Marketed over +\$1 billion in multifamily real estate transactions
- » Coordinate timeline and schedules with clients and photographers
- » Production of fliers, proposals and offering memorandums
- » Create property listing websites with Listing Lab interface
- » Video editing for property listings and uploading to websites
- » Conduct market research for the Central Texas office, national Manufacturing Housing group, and national Student Housing group
- » Maintain and schedule website launches and email blasting per listing
- Created database of national photographer list for marketing department
- * Adapted new email marketing campaign process for marketing department

GRAPHIC DESIGNER | NOV 2017 - May 2018 (Contractor) Texas Hospital Association, Austin, TX (Tasks/*Achievements)

- » Produced white pages from given context using THA branding
- » Create additional logo designs for following company branding
- » Communicate with team on "Basecamp" workflow tool

GRAPHIC+WEB DESIGNER / PHOTOGRAPHER | NOV 2014 - NOV 2017 The Carvajal Group, Austin, TX (Tasks/*Achievements)

- Design fliers, brochures, banners, direct mail, logos, and print materials
- » Produced MLS signs, billboard graphics, and magazine ads
- » Create and maintain WordPress website for per property listing
- » Drive to property listings to take exterior and interior photos
- » Post edit and finalize real estate photos for print and media
- » Direct mail campaign to specific strategized market region
- » Daily email blast campaign to specific clients and investors
- * Self-taught real estate photography & WordPress knowledge
- * Created branding for a new broker group used on social media

INTERN GRAPHIC DESIGNER | JAN 2012 - MAY 2012 Clockwork Studios, San Antonio, TX (Tasks/*Achievements)

- » Working on editorials, newsletters, and brochures
- » Created original logos for personal portfolio
- » Idea contribution & Poster design for clients in Seattle / San Antonio
- » Assist senior designers on design material and content
- * One of the pitched ideas to client was in final selection

Education

COMMUNICATION DESIGN | 2006 - 2010 BFA | Texas State University | San Marcos, TX Cum Laude Achievement | GPA: 3.7

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

» Dean's List 2019 & 2010

Skill set / Abilities

Design Softwares: Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, Dreamweaver, Flash, and Premiere

Web-based Application:

HTML/CSS, FTP Client and WordPress

Hand skills: Drawing, Painting, and Printmaking

Office Application:

MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Office 365, Mac, Windows

Photography:

Real Estate Photography and Lightroom post editing

Campaign E-blast Interface:

Listing Lab, CampaignBreeze, RealtyJuggler

References

Shawn Meeks

Design Professor at Fort Lewis College (Durango, Co) 210.382.9091 | scmeek@fortlewis.edu

Erik Le

Consumer Success Manager at Realtor.com (Austin, Tx) 512.998.3944 | erik.le1082@gmail.com

Jose Luis Salazar

UX Developer at Community Impact Newspaper (Austin, Tx) 512.940.8604 | choche_@hotmail.com